dinostorm.com 2016-04-02

# Data Privacy Policy

                            Data Privacy Policy
                                              of
                                Splitscreen Studios GmbH
                               Current as of: March 25, 2014
Splitscreen Studios GmbH (hereinafter referred to as “Provider”) operates interactive
games and applications on the internet (collectively referred to as “Services”).
The Provider takes data privacy matters very seriously and wishes to ensure that the
privacy of the Users is optimally protected when using the Services offered. The
following Data Privacy Policy defines how the personal data of Users is handled.
General Information
In principle, the internet offers can be accessed without having to state any personal
information. However, in order to be able to use the Provider’s Services, a User
Account and one or more play accounts must be created and the corresponding
access data enabled. This requires disclosing certain personal details to the Provider.
The Provider must be in possession of certain up-to-date personal data of the Users
at all times to be able to communicate with them (e.g. e-mail). In addition, for the
purchase of Premium Services, the User is required to disclose further personal
details so that payment transactions can be processed.
In such cases, the Provider shall observe the statutory regulations on data privacy, in
particular the regulations of the German Federal Data Protection Act (“BDSG”) and
the German Telemedia Act (“TMG”) at all times.
The Provider collects, processes and uses user data only where Users have given
their consent to do so or where a statutory provision permits the processing or use of
such. In such cases, only the data that is necessary to perform and make use of the
Services or that has been provided voluntarily shall be collected, processed and
used.
        1. Personal Data
Personal data is all data that contains details about the personal or material
circumstances of an identified or identifiable individual, in particular name, e-mail
address, age, gender, date of birth, physical address and bank account details.
        2. What data is collected and for what purposes is it used?
The following data is recorded for the specified purposes and occasions:
    a) User name, password and e-mail address are recorded for registration with
        online services. The e-mail address is recorded in order to be able to contact
        the User in the course of providing the Services, to be able to confirm
        registration, to be able to send a new password in the event that the password
                                         Page 1 of 4

        is lost, and to inform the User about any new regulations, offers, products or
        similar. The user name is recorded in order to be able to allocate the User a
        User Account.
    b) While the Services are being used by the User, the IP address of the computer
        on which the user logged in as well as the times and type of use are recorded.
        This data is recorded in order to be able to identify the individual responsible in
        the event of a breach of the rules and also to prevent a User from
        manipulating the Services offered or disrupting the operation of such Services.
    c) When ordering Premium Services or other chargeable Services, users’ credit
        card or bank account details (depending on the selected payment method) are
        recorded in order to be able to process the respective payments. In each case,
        the relevant data entered on the form by the User is recorded.
        3. Will the data be forwarded to third parties?
For processing payments due when ordering Premium Services or other chargeable
Services, it is necessary to forward personal data such as name, account number or
credit card details to third parties who process the payment transactions as contract
partners of the Provider. The Provider undertakes to ensure that any data transmitted
to third parties is processed and used for the intended purposes only.
        4. For how long is the data kept and when is it deleted?
The collected data shall only be kept as long as is necessary for the Provider to
provide the
Services or as required by statutory regulations. Data such as user name, password,
e-mail address, IP address of the computer used and the times and type of use shall
be kept until such time as the user’s user account is deleted. If a User cancels one of
his/her play accounts, the data relating to this shall be deleted. The data will be
deleted within a few days of cancellation.
The User may request at any time the deletion of specific or all data collected. If the
User requests that the e-mail address, user name, IP address of the computer used
and the times and type of use be deleted, this means that the corresponding User
Account and play accounts will also be deleted because it is then no longer possible
to
communicate with the User and/or the security of the games can no longer be
safeguarded.
        5. Are cookies used?
Cookies are text files which are sent to a browser by a web server or are otherwise
generated. The User’s computer sends information to the server each time it
accesses the Provider’s website. Cookies enable information to be stored on the
User’s computer and facilitate the use of websites as such websites can be optimally
adapted to the respective User, thereby enabling personal settings to be saved. The
                                         Page 2 of 4

Provider uses cookies in order to be able to identify Users without authentication and
to display the Services in the language last selected by them.
Cookies are also used to detect fraud. Where Users have set their browsers to
prevent the use of cookies, the functionality of the Services may be restricted or may
not function at all.
       6. Tracking
The Provider commissions third-party companies who use cookies to enable an
analysis of how the website is used by the respective User. The information
generated by the cookies is transmitted to a server operated by the Provider abroad
and stored there. The service provider will use this information to evaluate how the
Services are used, to compile reports for the Provider on User activity and to provide
further services connected with the use of the website. The service provider shall
also forward this information to third parties if necessary, insofar as this is legally
stipulated or insofar as third parties process this data on behalf of the service
provider. On no account will the service provider link your IP address with other data
of the service provider.
       7. How is the data secured?
In order to protect the security of the information during transmission, the Provider
uses encryption technology (including SSL) to encrypt the transmitted information.
The Provider also keeps physical, electronic and procedural safety measures in
connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of Users’ personal data. An
individual password is required to access the User Account.
       8. Information
The User may at any time request information on the type and scope of the data
stored by the Provider under their name and on the actual data itself. No charge shall
be levied for the disclosure of this information.
Consent to the collection and processing of data
By acknowledging the Provider’s General Terms and Conditions of Business, the
User hereby consents to the personal data specified, as well as the data generated
as a result of using the Services offered by the Provider, in particular IP address and
times and type of use, being recorded and stored.
I am aware that, should I refuse my consent, neither a User Account nor a play
account can be created and that, in such cases, the Services offered by the Provider
cannot be used.
The consent to the collection, storage and use of personal user data may be revoked
at any time with effect for the future. In such a case, the User Account and the play
account will be deleted as the collection, storage and use of the personal user data is
no longer required to monitor compliance with the rules of the applications.
                                         Page 3 of 4

Information on Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc.
("Google"). Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, text files, which are stored on
your computer and enable an analysis of how you use the site. The information
collected by the cookie on your use of this website (including your IP address) is
transmitted to a Google server in the US and stored there. Google will use this
information to evaluate how you use the website, to compile reports on site activities
for the website operators and to provide further services connected with the use of
the site and the Internet. Google will also forward this information to third parties if
necessary, insofar as this is legally stipulated or insofar as third parties process this
data on behalf of Google. On no account will Google link your IP address with other
Google data. You can prevent the installation of cookies on your computer by
adjusting your browser software accordingly; however, we must point out that, in this
case, not all functions of this website may be available to you in their full capacity. By
using this website, you thereby consent to the processing of the data recorded by
Google under your name in the manner described above and for the purpose(s)
specified above.
Contact
Please address any queries concerning the handling of the data to:
Ole Schaper
E-mail: support@splitscreenstudios.com
                                        Page 4 of 4
